upto75.com 2010-05-11

# UPto75: Never Miss A Sale: Privacy Policy - Great deals, offers, discounts and sales in stores in your city

### Categories

Cars, Bikes, Others 

Magazine Subscription, Books & Novels 

Womens, Mens, Baby & Kids 

CD and DVD, PC's and Laptops, Printers & Accessories, Software, Games & Consoles 

Schools, Colleges, Universities, Training Institutes 

Camera & Camcorders, Mobiles, MPS Players, TVs & DVD Players 

Food Items, Beverages 

Home, Office 

Flowers, Gifts, Greeting Cards 

Beauty Parlors, Cosmetics, Dentist & Eye Care, Hospitals, Spas & Therapy Centres 

Washing Machines, ACs & Refrigerators, Microwaves & Vacuums 

Bed & Bath, Kitchen & Dining, Cleaning & Storage, Other Household Items 

Holiday Packages 

Net Connections, Broadband, Domains & Hosting 

Gold, Pearls & Diamonds, Watches, Rings & Bracelets 

Baby Care, Strollers, Toys & Games 

Theme Parks, Dance Studios 

DVDs, Musical Instruments, Tickets 

Eateries, Restaurants, Fast Food, Pubs 

Astrology, Chartered Accountants, Tailoring & Laundry, Tax Consultants 

Gym & Health Clubs, Fitness Equipment, Sports Goods 

Airfares, Holiday Packages 

### Testimonials

When upto75.com approached us for promoting our offers through their site, we looked at the package rate for promotion and we were surprised how cost effective it was. Subsequently we got a fairly good response which even media advertisement campaigns could not fetch us. The concept is unique and well designed to attract the consumers who are nowadays very cautious about shopping- they do not wish to buy anything at M.R.P. Such consumers have a one stop solution to know the best offers active in the market. As a business associate, we were offered a quick, professional and pleasing service. Its a matter of time before all leading brands across all industries in this country try to find a place in upto75.com seeking leads.

- **M Santhosh- Sr Manager- Thyrocare** ,  
12-Apr-2010

Privacy Policy  
---  
UPto75.com respects the privacy of its users and is committed to protect it in all respects. UPto75.com reserves the right to revise this policy, from time to time in part or full depending upon its requirement, legislations and market conditions. Hence it requests its users to check the privacy policy on a periodic basis.   
   
**Scope**  
Our privacy policy explains how we handle both personally identifiable and anonymous information collected from our members and non-members and how that information might be used and shared.   
   
**Types of information that may be collected**  
Web Site Usage Information  
We may receive and store certain types of website usage information when you visit or interact with our site, e.g.: we may collect information typically but not restricted to about the page served, the time & the source of request, the type of browser making the request, preceding page viewed and other similar information along with your IP address or any other device identifier. This website usage information on analysis helps us to determine how visitors arrive at our website, what type of content is most popular, and what type of visitors are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising.  
Information You Provide Us   
User may be asked to provide us with certain personal information for membership purposes like name, e-mail address, contact number, and physical address.   
Information from Other Sources  
We may receive information about you from other sources; e.g. we may obtain geographic or demographic information, or information regarding your possible interests, from third parties, or we may receive information from a marketing partner. We may combine the information we receive from those other sources with information we collect through the Web Site.   
Refer A Friend   
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. UPto75.com does not store your friend�s name and email address after sending the one-time email.   
   
**How information may be collected**  
We use cookies and other Internet technologies to enrich your online experience by managing our website and email programs. Our cookies do not contain any information, in itself, that is personally identifiable.   
Cookies  
If your browser is set to allow cookies, we may store small amounts of information on your computer about what parts of our websites you have visited and what features you like best. We may then tailor the content you see to match your interests. We also may use cookies to identify members so that they don't have to re-enter their usernames and passwords. Cookies may also be used to limit the number of advertisements you see while on our site. By allowing us to understand how you use our site over time, cookies will help us provide you with a better and more relevant online experience.  
Some ads on our site are provided by outside companies. If these ads contain cookies, they can be accessed only by those advertisers; we do not have access to them. Most browsers allow you to modify your security to accept or reject cookies. You need not have cookies turned on to visit our site, but without them, your access to some areas may be limited and custom navigation may not be available to you.   
Pixel Tags   
UPto75.com may use pixel tags, also known as web beacons. Pixel tags help us improve our understanding of our web traffic and visitor behaviour, as well as gauge the response to our various promotional efforts. This information is non-personally identifiable and is used for an aggregate picture of how visitors use our site.   
   
**How we use the information collected**  
The information you provide to us may be used to: 

  * Send you alerts or newsletters and/or other communications for which you have registered; 
  * Provide special offers or promotional materials to you on behalf of us or third parties; Many of our members appreciate receiving these offers. However, you will always be able to opt out receiving future third party offers. 
  * Monitor or improve the Web Sites; 
  * Customize the advertising and content you see 

Moreover, if you submit comments or other content to the website, it maybe published online or offline along with your name. Please also check out our Terms of Use.  

**With whom information may be shared**  
Third parties providing services on our behalf  
We employ third parties to perform functions on our behalf; examples include hosting or operating Web Sites, sending e-mail and/or other communications, providing wireless services, removing repetitive information from customer lists, data analysis, marketing assistance, and customer service. These third parties may have access to your personal information for the purpose of performing such functions on the Web Sites' behalf.   
Non-Personal Information  
We may share non-personal information, such as aggregate user statistics, demographic information, and web site usage information with third parties.   
When You Agree To Receive Information From Third Parties  
You may be presented with an opportunity to receive information and/or marketing/ sale offers from third party(s). Your personal information will only be shared with other third party(s) for marketing purposes with out your prior approval. If you do agree to have your personal information shared, your personal information will be disclosed to such third party(s) and all information you disclose will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of such third party(s). We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of such third party(s) and, therefore, you should review the privacy policies and practices of such third party(s) prior to agreeing to receive such information from third party(s). If you later decide that you no longer want to receive communication from a third party, you will need to contact that third party directly.   
Sweepstakes, Contests and Promotions  
We may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions through the Web Sites that may require registration. If you choose to enter a sweepstakes, contest or other promotion, your personal information may be disclosed to third parties in connection with the administration of such promotion, including, without limitation, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law, such as on a winners list. Also, by entering a promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor(s) of the promotion to use your name, voice and/or likeness in advertising or marketing associated with the promotion.  
Business Transfers  
In the case of a change of ownership or a merger involving UPto75.com, personally identifiable information would be one of those transferred assets.   
**Law Enforcement**  
We may disclose information about our users, including personal information, in the event we are required to respond to law enforcement agencies.   
   
**Choice/Opt-out**  
If you do not wish to continue receiving our e-mail newsletters or bulletins you can opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking on the unsubcribe link.   
   
**Security**  
UPto75.com incorporates reasonable safeguards to help protect and secure your personal information. However, no data transmission over the Internet, or wireless transmission, or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please note that UPto75.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to the Web Site, and you do so at your own risk.
